recruitmentplatform.com 2015-06-21

# Privacy Policy | Lumesse

One of the fundamentals of the relationship with Lumesse - in fact of any relationship - is trust. With Lumesse, you can trust that we are 100% committed to protecting your privacy on our website. We will also use our best efforts to ensure that information you might submit to us by use of our website remains confidential, and is used only for the dedicated purposes as described below.

The following Privacy Policy serves to inform you about our privacy commitment regarding your visits to our website under [www.lumesse.com](http://www.lumesse.com/) (hereinafter referred to as the "website"). You can save this Privacy Policy to your computer by pressing CTRL+S, and you can print it by pressing CTRL+P.

**What information we collect and for what purposes**

When you visit our website, the servers on which our website is hosted automatically process the data that are sent to them by your own web browser. This data, of which some may be classified as personal data, contains information about:

  * The type and version of your browser
  * The operating system of your computer
  * The URL from which you came to our website
  * Your Internet protocol address (IP address)
  * The time of your visit

We use the information listed above to create statistics in order to measure the number of visitors to our website, and to improve our website. We do not draw up user profiles or link the above mentioned data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are collected and stored by us for a limited period, as far as this is necessary and permissible for data safety reasons.

**Sharing data**

In general, we do not share with third parties any personal data related to your visit of our website.

However, please note that our website may be hosted on servers of a third party service provider, which will process the data listed above under "What information we collect and for what purposes". Also, other companies from within the Lumesse company group may act as technical service provider(s) for us in regard to running this website and, if available, possible additional services (as described below under "Additional services"). You consent that we may share your personal data and information provided for the purposes stated above in compliance with this paragraph.

**Cookies**

We use cookies on our website - small files (containing a text-only string of information) that a website transfers to the cookie file of your computer's hard disk. We may use both persistent cookies as well as temporary cookies which are deleted after you close your browser. Cookies may be used to help us recognise your computer (just a number) when you return to our website. They may also allow us to compile aggregated statistics that help us improve the structure of our website.

You have the possibility to accept or decline cookies by simply modifying the settings in your browser.

**Editing and deletion of your data**

You have a right to ask for rectification and/or deletion of your data. You also have the right to object at any time, free of charge to the processing of your personal data for future use, and you also have right of access to your data and the right to receive information from us concerning your data. You can claim these rights by contacting us; our contact details can be found [here](http://www.lumesse.com/legal-information "Legal information").

**IT Security**

We use a variety of methods, such as intrusion detection software and manual security procedures, to help ensuring IT security. Please note that JavaScript technology is used on our website.

**Your Information and Additional Services**

Through this website we will collect information that can identify you, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and other similar information ("Your Information") when it is voluntarily submitted to us by you. We will use Your Information to respond to requests you may make of us, and from time to time, we may refer to Your Information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our websites, products and services.

We may also provide specific services on our website like contact forms, newsletter subscription forms, downloads and/or online tools. For the use of these services you might have to provide additional information and the use of such services may be subject to additional terms. If so, these additional terms will be brought to your attention before you use the respective services.

**Links**

Our website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware of this when they leave our website, and to read the privacy policy of such websites linked to when visiting them. This Privacy Policy applies only to our website.

**Protection of minors**

You should be aware that this site is not intended for, or designed to attract, individuals under the age of 18. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is an individual under the age of 18.

**Privacy Policy changes**

Any possible changes to our privacy commitment for our website will always be reflected in alterations of or amendments to this Privacy Policy so that our visitors are always aware of what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to third parties.

**Miscellaneous**

If you should have any concerns or queries in relation to our Privacy Policy please contact us. You find our contact details [here](http://www.lumesse.com/legal-information "Legal information").

**Lumesse, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework**

Lumesse, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Lumesse, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Lumesse, Inc.'s certification, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor)
